Gag (I’m not sure what Gya Gya Gya~~~ su means literally.)
Just a little more, Esra!
How interesting…
Never in a thousand years did I imagine a human being born with this kind of power was possible.
It's truly... a miracle.
A child wielding miraculous power.
Esra… you did well hanging in there.
It's a beautiful baby boy.
His name… is Sinbad.
A child who will become king of the seven seas.
Scenery I've never seen before…
Strange beasts…
Humid and warm air...
This is... a Dungeon!
The Conquest of Dungeon Baal ・ Part 2
Crap!
Don't break formation!
Move forward along the cliff!
What the hell?
A one-hundred-man unit… gone in a flash…
In... In a place like this…
Come at me, beast!
Y-You!
This way!
Hurry up!
But how did you get here before me?
I was the first one to enter.
You're the brat who refused to enlist.
Don't do something you'll regret.
Huh?
I'm a soldier.
There's no reason I should have been saved by an unpatriotic person who defies his own country.
I don't care about your reasons.
I saved your life, so deal with it.
You didn't even bother to thank me.
Look who's childish now.
I’m childish?!
Fine. I’ll explain things in terms that even commoners like you can understand.
Burn it in your head.
My beautiful name.
I am the youngest of the Parthevia Empire's Dragul lineage,
Son of General Draguliel Hendrius Nodomis Pertegomidus,
Lieutenant of the Western Region Military Unit,
Dragul Nol Henrius Govius Menudias Partenuvonomias Dumid Os Kartanon.
Too long.
I’ll shorten it to Drakon.
Huh? What?
I said I’ll just call you Drakon.
That's rude!
There’s no way I’ll remember all that!
I'm just Sinbad, and that's all there is to it!
How dare you mock the Dragul family name!
Die!
Apparently…
It looks like we don't have time to be messing around.
Just look at the size of it.
Is he the Dragon King or something?
He just ate those he didn't like.
Though he's a Dragon King, he resmbles a human King perfectly.
Shut your mouth, you commoner!
To proceed any further, you need to do something about him, huh?
This is where we put our lives on the line.
We're being tested.
Tested, you say?
Sinbad, was it?
I'll make you my subordinate for now.
Huh?
Be my decoy. Distract him.
While you do, I'll head for the door.
This is a test of whether we can achieve our goal despite making sacrifices.
It's a test of determination.
Now, go!
Hey, don't make decisions on your own.
A commoner like you will be helping our country.
Be honored.
If you're killed in action, I'll give you a reward.
Just stop it.
You're really a fool of the military.
How many people have died with that mindset?!
Be brave and stay.
Lay down your life for your country.
That is the pride of the Parthevian army.
Dying for your country means satisfaction.
What troublesome geysers.
I have no idea where they'll erupt next.
And these baby dragons…
The gates…
If I can just open the gates!
I did it!
I made it to the gate!
Now, open!
Oh Gate, open!
Why?
But why?!
These are…
Open. Open, open, open, open!
No… no way, this isn't happening.
I'm definitely going to die.
No, not yet…
I don't want to die yet!
Serendine-sama, First Princess of the Parthevian Empire.
Lieutenant General Barbarossa-sama, eldest of the Dragul Family Line,
Congratulations.
This marriage is the first step towards glory for the Parthevian Empire.
Well said, my brother.
You moron!
Hey, get a hold of yourself.
Get up, or you'll die!
Kill…
...Kill me!
Fearing the enemy while clinging to my position…
I’ve failed as a soldier.
Bullshit.
Be brave and stay.
Give your life for your country?
What's wrong with not wanting to die?
It's so obvious!
You're a human before you're a soldier!
Dying for your country like that…
Have the empire, the army, saved the people at least once?
A country exists to protect the people living in it.
It shouldn't encourage war and pushing them to their deaths.
A country that discards its people… isn't needed!
I’m borrowing this.
Hey, you!
You hear that, Drakon?!
Those with power making sacrifices for their surroundings.
It's the sound of accepting punishment.
It opened.
Let's go.
Just what the hell are you?!
It’s not what I am. It’s who I am.
I'm Sinbad the sailor!
Sinbad…
What a strange man.
When you think he's an idiot who casts away his life,
he's actually calmly analyzing the situation.
He makes the right choices at the right time and place.
A man that rides on the wave of fate.
We're here, huh?
This is the deepest part of the Dungeon.
Is your face turning blue yet?
You're breathing pretty heavily yourself.
Speak for yourself! Don't your feet hurt from running so much?
That's because some idiot put me in a position where I had to!
However, I praise you for doing well, for a commoner.
And I thought you were some spoiled kid, but you've got some backbone.
But not as much as I do, though.
That's my line.
Everything's made of stone.
Nothing seems off, though.
No, it doesn't feel that way to me.
My name is Baal.
I am the Djinn of Wrath and Heroes.
Who is to become king?
Is this what Yunan was talking about? The power to become a king?
The power that the wizards were talking about. If I can present this to his Majesty...
In that case…
The one who'll become king…
Is me!
Don't interfere, Drakon.
I'm here with official orders from the Imperial Royalty.
Stand down.
To hell with your official order.
I won't give any more power to those who step over the innocent.
I've decided.
I'll change this country – no, this world – with my own hands!
So in the end, we have to settle the score.
I owe you for saving my life.
But I'm still a Parthevian soldier.
And I won't waver either.
Let us see who shall become my master.
You're pretty good.
But still…!
Sinbad, you may be strong, but
I'm not weak either!
Goodbye.
It's true you're a better swordsman.
But this isn't a battle of who's better with a sword!
I'm losing consciousness…
I promise that this conquest for the Dungeon will be a success.
I absolutely will not hurt Serendine-sama's name.
Don't be so serious.
Your forehead will get wrinkles.
Besides, I'm known as the Venomous Spider Princess.
What's there to hurt?
I've taken a liking to having two names.
Shoot a web.
Weaken the opponent, and kill them.
I'm exactly like a spider that never lets her prey get away.
So in your case, I'm more tenacious than you think.
That's why, Dragul…
Dying is unforgivable.
I can't lose yet…
I haven't lost yet!
I can…
I can still keep going!
Brother.
Serendine-sama is a beautiful, smart, and strong princess.
I'm sure you got to know her plenty yesterday.
I support you both from the bottom of my hea---
Junior. Aren't you misunderstanding something?
This engagement is just like a foolish festival.
It's just so the Dragul family can rebuild this weakening country.
So about the princess…
I don't love her.
I couldn't say anything.
I couldn't do anything.
I couldn't protect the princess,
nor could I tell her my feelings, either.
It's frustrating.
My own… My own weakness is frustrating.
But even so, I have things to protect.
I know.
I have my own reasons for not losing, either.
That's why…
I…
...can't lose!
I win.
I've bared witness.
I now acknowledge you as my master.
Receive this!
This is the power that many have desired.
The First Dungeon Baal
Conquest Completed
It's a soldier.
An unconscious soldier!
Great job, young conqueror.
You're now honored as a young soldier.
You've done well.
Now, please hand over the loot and the Dungeon's power.
Don't lump me in with you lot.
This power and treasure is something that I worked for.
I'll never hand them over to you.
What did you say?!
He's rebelling against the empire!
Get him!
Aren't you going to use the power you just earned?
Yunan!
Oh, that's right.
You don't know how to use those powers yet.
Do you need my assistance already, master?
A blue giant!
What is that? A monster?!
Now, follow what your heart is telling you.
O spirit of wrath and heroes.
I command you to slay a thousand-fold.
Use my magoi and will to enhance your power.
Come forth, Baal!
This is… my power?!
Sinbad.
Yunan? What's going on?!
It'll take two days by boat, right?
This a service of goodwill from me.
That was the first time I've ever flown.
Sin-nii-chan?
It really is Sin-nii-chan!
I'm back, everyone.
Where have you been?!
I conquered a Dun—
Where were you for two months, leaving Esra-san alone?!
Dear… is that you?
You're back.
If I can see you,
It means I must be going soon.
You know, in that brief moment,
when he took your sword and went on his adventure...
He was happy, confident, and overdoing it like a fool.
But he treasures his family and friends.
He really is a kind child, just like you.
But he's grown up now.
I'm sure he's okay.
I love you… Sin…
You've found it, haven't you?
Something that only you can do.
Go and do what you have to do.
I'll be fine.
Since then, Sinbad's name spread far and wide throughout Parthevia.
And when news of how the Dungeon that was challenged by over 10,000 men
was conquered by a 14-year-old boy,
the war-torn started to feel encouragement.
On the other hand, the little commoner hero was seen as an eyesore to royalty.
They couldn't allow him to do as he pleased.
A plan to capture him was set up.
Listen.
Sinbad will surely take his leave from this point.
Be sure to arrest him and bring him here.
Yes ma'am!
For the princess to have to come here herself…
How deplorable.
Don't say that.
We don't have enough troops to send out right now.
It's just me and my guards.
Besides…
We won't do your bidding anymore!
Sinbad sold his treasures and bought a boat!
Who would ever follow an incompetent idiot who's interested in nothing but war?!
Go home, you dogs!
Move!
I won't allow you to insult my father.
I'll cut off your tongue and set you on fire!
Stop.
That young boy…
You're Sinbad, aren't you?
Oh? I'm glad a pretty lady like you knows my name.
How dare you! Don't you know who she is?
This is Serendine-sama, First Princess of the Parthevian Empire!
Parthevia's Venomous Spider Princess?!
Let me show you what happens to people that treat me like a pampered lady.
Unfortunately, I don't like hurting girls—
Stop spouting off!
You fight well for someone with a pretty face.
But you can't beat me.
Do you know why people call me the Venomous Spider Princess?
I'm aware that people from other lands call me that.
That being said…
That's poison from Desert king spiders.
What's so funny?
Good thing I took this on the fly.
That's the antidote!
Don't tell me… he took it from my pocket back then?
And with that, I'm taking her hostage.
Stop it!
Don't interfere until I get on my boat.
Princess!
Damn you, put me down!
What are you doing?!
How dare you put me through this kind of embarrassment!
S-Stay back. Don't touch me!
Stop!
Your soldiers can fetch you from this distance, right?
Thanks for letting me take you hostage, pretty lady.
Never... I'll never forgive you, Sinbad!
Let's go.
I'm going to change the world!